The American Center of Polish Culture records CPAA.09.04
Connecticut Polish American Archives
- Administrative
  - Oversize- Miscellaneous Photos; 2 Photo Albums; Court documents from Karski Bequest, 2003; Membership & Mailing lists, 1990-2003 (Box 16)
  - Oversize- Binder of Membership lists from various Polish/American organizations [2001]; General Pulaski Memorial Day Proclamation, 1996; Center Line (1993-2008); Polish & American Flag (Box 17)
- Financial
  - ACPCC Washington Project- Donations, 1985-1987 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - ACPCC Washington Project- Raffle- Donors and deposits, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - ACPCC Washington Project- Putnam Hi Income Government Trust, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - ACPCC Washington Project- Raffle- Expenses and Income, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - ACPCC Washington Project- Money market fund- The Fidelity Trust Company, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - ACPCC Washington Project- Money market account, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - ACPCC Washington Project- Paid expenses, 1986-1988 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - ACPCC Washington Project- Expenses paid, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - ACPCC Washington Project- Donor list, 1985-1989 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - ACPCC Washington Project- Banking papers, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - ACPCC Washington Project- Banking Papers, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - ACPCC Washington Project- Income and expenses, 1987-1989 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - ACPCC Washington Project- Tax return, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - ACPCC Washington Project- Financial correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - ACPC- Financial Audit, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - ACPC- Banking papers, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - ACPC- Expenses paid, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - ACPC- Income and expenses, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - ACPC- Annual Report, Tax form, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - ACPC- Financial correspondence and reports, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - ACPC- Banking records- Rigg's account, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - ACPC- Budget, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - ACPC- Connecticut National Bank Statements, donations, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - ACPC- Expenses paid, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - ACPC- Banking accounts paperwork (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - ACPC- Financial review, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - ACPC- Washington Center Building Closing, 1991-1993 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - ACPC- First National Bank of Stamford Account, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - ACPC- Connecticut National Bank account, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - ACPC- Financial Statement Review, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - ACPC- Donation lists, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - ACPC- Center renovation expenses, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - ACPC- Expenses paid., 1992 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - ACPC- CD's accounts, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - ACPC- Rigg's Bank checking account, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - ACPC- Chevy Chase account, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - ACPC- All accounts binder, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - ACPC- Pledges/Matching gifts, 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - ACPC- Tax forms, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - ACPC- Tax forms, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - ACPC- Riggs Bank checking account, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - ACPC- First National Bank of Stamford- Donations, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - ACPC- Center audit- Financial Report, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - ACPC- Donation lists, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - ACPC- Expenses paid., 1993 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - ACPC- Income and expenses binder., 1993 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - ACPC- Merrill Lynch bank account, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - ACPC- Chevy Chase bank account, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - ACPC- Income and expenses binder, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - ACPC- Center audit- Financial Report, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - ACPC- Donation lists, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - ACPC- Cornerstone Bank account, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - ACPC- Expenses, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - ACPC- Tax forms, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - ACPC- Chevy Chase bank account, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - ACPC- Merrill Lynch bank account, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - ACPC- Riggs Bank checking account, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - ACPC- Tax forms- 990, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - ACPC- Connecticut Sales Tax Exemption papers, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - ACPC- Expenses paid, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - ACPC- Prudential Securities account, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - ACPC- Chevy Chase account, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - ACPC- Income and expenses binder, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - ACPC- Cornerstone Bank account, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - ACPC- Riggs Bank checking account, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - ACPC- Merrill Lynch bank account, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - ACPC- Property tax problem- Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - ACPC- Donation lists, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - ACPC- Joel Barlow Memorial Fund, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - ACPC- Promotion of boat donations, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - ACPC- Tax forms- 990, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - ACPC- Raffle Income, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - ACPC- Donation lists, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - ACPC- Expenses paid, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - ACPC- Prudential Securities account, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - ACPC- Tax forms and financial review, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - ACPC- Income and expenses monthly reports, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - ACPC- Payroll, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - ACPC- Chevy Chase account, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - ACPC- Cornerstone Bank account, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - ACPC- Riggs Bank checking account, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - ACPC- Chevy Chase account, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - ACPC- Chevy Chase account- Karski Scholarship Fund, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - ACPC- Riggs Bank checking account, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - ACPC- Income and expenses monthly reports, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - ACPC- Tax forms- 990, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - ACPC- Donation lists, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - ACPC- Profit & Loss Statements, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - ACPC- Expenses paid, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - ACPC- Donation lists- Connecticut Donors, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - ACPC- Cornerstone Bank account, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - ACPC- Donation lists, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - ACPC- Chevy Chase account, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - ACPC- Chevy Chase account- Karski Scholarship Fund, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - ACPC- Riggs Bank checking account, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - ACPC- Tax forms, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - ACPC- Cornerstone Bank account, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - ACPC- Income and expenses monthly reports, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - ACPC- SmithBarney Endowment Fund, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - ACPC- Expenses paid, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - ACPC- Donations of matching gifts, 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - ACPC- Insurance statements, 1992-2000 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - ACPC- Income and expenses monthly reports, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - ACPC- SmithBarney Endowment Fund, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - ACPC- Tax forms and financial review, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - ACPC- Chevy Chase account, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - ACPC- Cornerstone Bank account, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - ACPC- Riggs Bank checking account, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - ACPC- Monthly Reports, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - ACPC- Riggs Bank checking account, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - ACPC- Purchase of Washington Building & donations, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - ACPC- Chevy Chase account, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - ACPC- Program reports (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - ACPC- Cornerstone Bank account, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - ACPC- Citicorp Investment Services, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - ACPC- Payroll taxes, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - ACPC- Niziol Inheritance, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - ACPC- Chevy Chase account- Karski Scholarship Fund, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - ACPC- Chevy Chase account- Children's Fund, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - ACPC- Donation lists, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - ACPC- Connecticut Donors, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - ACPC- Profit & Loss Statements, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - ACPC- Estates and wills in process, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - ACPC- Expenses, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - ACPC- Tax forms- 990, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - ACPC- Chevy Chase account, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - ACPC- Chevy Chase account- Karski Scholarship Fund, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - ACPC- Riggs Bank checking account, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - ACPC- Cornerstone Bank account, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - ACPC- Monthly Reports, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - ACPC- Citicorp Investment Services, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - ACPC- Payroll, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - ACPC- Chevy Chase account- Children's Fund, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - ACPC- Profit & Loss Statements, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - ACPC- Expenses, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - ACPC- Cornerstone Bank account, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - ACPC- Tax forms and financial review, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - ACPC- Cornerstone Bank Account, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - ACPC- Chevy Chase account, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - ACPC- Chevy Chase account- Children's Fund, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - ACPC- Chevy Chase account- Karski Scholarship Fund, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - ACPC- Riggs Bank checking account, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - ACPC- Citicorp Investment Services, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - ACPC- Monthly Reports, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - ACPC- Expenses, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - ACPC- Wachovia Checking Account, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - ACPC- Donation lists, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - ACPC- Tax forms- 990, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - ACPC- Chevy Chase account, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - ACPC- Chevy Chase account- Karski Scholarship Fund, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - ACPC- Chevy Chase account- Children's Fund, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - ACPC- Tax forms- 990, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - ACPC- Estate of Joseph Furgal, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - ACPC- Riggs Bank checking account, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - ACPC- Wachovia Checking Account, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - ACPC- Center Expenses, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - ACPC- Profit & Loss Statements, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - ACPC- Donation lists, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - ACPC- Donation lists- From Connecticut, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - ACPC- Monthly Reports, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - ACPC- Citicorp Investment Services, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - ACPC- Profit & Loss Statements, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - ACPC- Payroll Information for taxes, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - ACPC- Expenses, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - ACPC- Insurance policy, 2005-2006 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - ACPC- Citicorp Investment Services, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - ACPC- Tax Forms and Audit, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - ACPC- Monthly Reports, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - ACPC- Wachovia Checking Account, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - ACPC- Chevy Chase account, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - ACPC- First National Bank- Money Market Account, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - ACPC- PNC Bank Account, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - ACPC- Polonia Bank Account, 1998-2006 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - ACPC- Expenses, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - ACPC- Insurance policy, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - ACPC- Wachovia Checking Account, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - ACPC- Chevy Chase account, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - ACPC- First County Bank- Money Market Account, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - ACPC- Karski Estate- Ammended, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - ACPC- PNC Bank Account, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - ACPC- Payroll, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - ACPC- Citicorp Investment Services, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - ACPC- Monthly Reports, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - ACPC- Audit, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - ACPC- Tax Forms, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - ACPC- Chevy Chase account, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - ACPC- Washington Mutual- CD Account, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - ACPC- PNC Bank Account, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - ACPC- Citicorp Investment Services, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - ACPC- Wachovia Checking Account, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - ACPC- Polonia Bank Account, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - ACPC- First County Bank- Money Market Account, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - ACPC- Budget, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - ACPC- Matching Gifts and Donations, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - ACPC- Tax forms- 990, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - ACPC- name change to the National Polish Center and election of a new treasurer., 2008 (Box 15, Folder 22)